[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "round": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The Velocipede was a nineteenth-century prototype of what?",
        "answer": "A bicycle"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "round": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "What plant is featured on the Canadian flag?",
        "answer": "Maple"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "round": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Eric Carle wrote a series of children's books about A Very Hungry ... what?",
        "answer": "Caterpillar"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "round": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "What is the world’s largest land mammal?",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "round": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Rio de Janeiro is a city in which South American country?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "round": "Music",
        "question": "Who was the lead singer of the band Queen until his death in 1991",
        "answer": "Freddie Mercury"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "round": "Music",
        "question": "Baby, Sporty, Ginger, Posh, and Scary are the nicknames of which UK girl band?",
        "answer": "Spice Girls"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "round": "Music",
        "question": "What is the name of the UK National Anthem?",
        "answer": "God Save The Queen"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "round": "Music",
        "question": "On what day of the week is the Official UK Singles Chart announced?",
        "answer": "Friday"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "round": "Music",
        "question": "Which famous male singer released a song called 'There's Nothing Holdin' Me Back'?",
        "answer": "Shawn Mendes"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "round": "Star Trek",
        "question": "What type of tea does Jean-Luc Picard prefer?",
        "answer": "Earl Grey (hot)"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "round": "Star Trek",
        "question": "Who is the Chief Morale Officer aboard the USS Voyager",
        "answer": "Neelix"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "round": "Star Trek",
        "question": "What species is known for their warnings \"Resistance is Futile\" and \"You will be assimilated\"?",
        "answer": "The Borg"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "round": "Star Trek",
        "question": "What is the first name of Captain Archer of the USS Enterprise NX01?",
        "answer": "Jonathan"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "round": "Star Trek",
        "question": "What furry species is known for the fact that it is born pregnant?",
        "answer": "Tribble"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "round": "History",
        "question": "How many of Henry VIII’s wives were called Anne?",
        "answer": "Two – Anne Boleyn and Anne of Cleves"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "round": "History",
        "question": "In which city was Titanic built?",
        "answer": "Belfast"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "round": "History",
        "question": "How many children did Queen Victoria have?",
        "answer": "Nine"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "round": "History",
        "question": "What year did World War One begin?",
        "answer": 1914
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "round": "History",
        "question": "What nationality was the famous explorer Captain James Cook?",
        "answer": "British"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "round": "Sport",
        "question": "What is the highest score possible in darts, in a single turn?",
        "answer": "One hundred and eighty"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "round": "Sport",
        "question": "Which Olympic sport is played with stones and brooms?",
        "answer": "Curling"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "round": "Sport",
        "question": "What colours make up the Olympic rings?",
        "answer": "Blue, Black, Red, Yellow and Green"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "round": "Sport",
        "question": "How many gold medals did team GB win at the Sochi Winter Olympics in 2014?",
        "answer": "One (Lizzy Yarnold, Skeleton)"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "round": "Sport",
        "question": "Who is the manager of Liverpool Football Club",
        "answer": "Jurgen Klopp"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "round": "The United Kingdom",
        "question": "What city is the capital of the UK",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "round": "The United Kingdom",
        "question": "What is the name of the flag of the UK",
        "answer": "Union flag/Union Jack"
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "round": "The United Kingdom",
        "question": "What city is the capital of Wales",
        "answer": "Cardiff"
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "round": "The United Kingdom",
        "question": "What is the London residence of Her Majesty The Queen?",
        "answer": "Buckingham Palace"
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "round": "The United Kingdom",
        "question": "What city is the capital of Northern Ireland?",
        "answer": "Belfast"
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "round": "Food and Drink",
        "question": "How many calories are in a glass of water?",
        "answer": "Zero"
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "round": "Food and Drink",
        "question": "What nuts are used to make marzipan?",
        "answer": "Almonds"
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "round": "Food and Drink",
        "question": "What animal does venison meat come from?",
        "answer": "Deer"
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "round": "Food and Drink",
        "question": "What type of sugar is found in milk?",
        "answer": "Lactose"
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "round": "Food and Drink",
        "question": "What country does Paella come from?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "round": "Science",
        "question": "What is the main source of vitamin C?",
        "answer": "Fruits"
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "round": "Science",
        "question": "What does a Geiger Counter measure?",
        "answer": "Radiation"
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "round": "Science",
        "question": "What is paleontology the study of?",
        "answer": "Fossils"
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "round": "Science",
        "question": "What gas makes fizzy drinks fizzy?",
        "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "round": "Science",
        "question": "Who is best known for his theory of black holes?",
        "answer": "Stephen Hawking"
    }
]
